Grabbing 20 random questions from the Spider dataset (seed=10)

Question 1: What are the full names of the 3 instructors who teach the most courses?
Database: college_3

Question 2: List the nominees that have been nominated more than two musicals.
Database: musical

Question 3: display all the information of those employees who did not have any job in the past.
Database: hr_1

Question 4: What is the alphabetically ordered list of all the distinct names of nurses?
Database: hospital_1

Question 5: Find the name and address of the customers who have both New and Pending orders.
Database: department_store

Question 6: What is the total and maximum duration of trips with bike id 636?
Database: bike_1

Question 7: What are the names of artist whose exhibitions draw over 200 attendees on average?
Database: theme_gallery

Question 8: Return the login names of the students whose family name is "Ward".
Database: e_learning

Question 9: List phone number and email address of customer with more than 2000 outstanding balance.
Database: driving_school

Question 10: List the name of ships that are not involved in any mission
Database: ship_mission

Question 11: Find the faculty rank that has the least members.
Database: activity_1

Question 12: What are the names of entrepreneurs?
Database: entrepreneur

Question 13: Which problem log was created most recently? Give me the log id.
Database: tracking_software_problems

Question 14: How many staff in total?
Database: driving_school

Question 15: What is the date of the performance with the highest number of attendees?
Database: performance_attendance

Question 16: Find the name and email of the user whose name contains the word æSwiftÆ.
Database: twitter_1

Question 17: How many people have membership in the club "Pen and Paper Gaming"?
Database: club_1

Question 18: List the nations that have more than two ships.
Database: ship_mission

Question 19: Which parties have more than 20 hosts? Give me the host names for these parties.
Database: party_host

Question 20: What is title of album which track Balls to the Wall belongs to?
Database: store_1

